KATHY WHITE | SOFTWARE ENGINEER

My Portfolio | My Github | My LinkedIn

Bloomington, IL ◆ 309-242-5871 ◆ <u>kawhite8503@gmail.com</u>

Former Radiologic Technologist of 11.5 years, turned Software Engineer, eager to contribute to success			
through hard work, attention to detail and excellent organizational skills. Equally successful in both			
team and self-directed settings. Excellent reputation for resolving problems and improving operation			
workflow. Motivated to learn, grow and excel in an exciting, thriving industry!			
TECHNICAL SKILLS			
HTML CSS JavaScript Node Express MongoDB Mongoose React Python PostgreSQL Django Responsive Web Design Git Github			
——————————————————————————————————————			
General Assembly			
 Completed 12-week 450+ hour Immersive Software Engineering course in May 2022 			
 Created a four-model travel organizing app utilizing MVC architecture and Google OAuth 			
 Developed skills using product development fundamentals, object-oriented programming, MVC 			

Projects -

Personal Portfolio | Solo Project

Live | Github

- Get to know more about me!
- Technologies used: HTML, Javascript, CSS, git, Node.js, Netlify

frameworks, data modeling, and team collaboration strategies.

Travel Prep App | Solo Project

Live | Github

- MEN stack application that helps you stay organized while traveling.
- Technologies used: HTML, Javascript, CSS, git, Node.js, MongoDB, Google OAuth, Heroku

<Third Project> | Team Project

Live | Github

- <Project description>
- <Technologies used: HTML, Javascript, CSS, git, Node.js, MongoDB, Google OAuth, Heroku>

_	Work HISTORY	
---	--------------	--

CT Scan Technologist, 10/2010 to 5/2022

Downstate Diagnostic Laboratories - Normal, IL

- Facilitated positive care experience for patients, establishing rapport and applying interpersonal skills to reduce anxiety and promote cooperation.
- Demonstrated financial responsibility and accountability through proper use of resources in daily procedures, processes, and practices as well as inventory/supply management.
- Developed and implemented innovative process improvements, work practices and equipment changes to improve productivity and enhance operations.
- Supervised the CT department, maintaining quality control standards and biannual IAC department accreditation.

Radiologic Technologist, 12/2009 to 10/2010

BroMenn Medical Center - Normal, IL

- Gained experience working several different shifts, lengths ranging from 8-12 hours.
- Collaborated with multiple departments, facilities, and physicians regarding patient care.
- Completed all written and electronic documentation, recognizing any discrepancies and addressing them in a timely fashion.

Customer Service Representative, 05/2006 to 12/2007

State Farm Insurance Inc – Bloomington, IL

- Maintained customer satisfaction with forward-thinking strategies focused on addressing customer needs and resolving concerns.
- Entered customer interaction details electronically to track requests, document problems and record solutions offered, in a fast-paced environment.
- Answered constant flow of customer calls with up to 20 calls in queue per minute

EDUCATION —
oftware Engineering Immersive (SEI)
General Assembly
Radiologic Technologist Certification Bloomington-Normal School of Radiography - Normal, IL
Associate of Arts Heartland Community College - Normal, IL
Certification/Licensure ————————————————————————————————————

Software Engineering: Software Engineering Certificate

Radiology: ARRT registered technologist, IEMA accreditation, IAC CT accreditation